Guide to the Tom Law San Francisco Bay Area Punk and Rock Handbill and Poster Collection M1976
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Posters, 3 manuscript boxes, 2 flat boxes and 1 large map folder
  - Folder 16, 1983- 1986 (Box 3)
    4. Sea Hags, The Stand, Bird Killers; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-06?; 8.5x17.
    5. Slovenly, Vomit Launch, The Idiot; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-15; 8.5x17.
    6. Every Song Released By Joy Division Will Be Played … On KALX; 1986-05-18; 8.5x17.
    7. Resistance. Solidarity. Against The Grain. Benefit For The Arts Brigade To Nicaragua. Mural Films and Slides. Invertebrate Music Looters Nic. Video, Dancing, Refreshments; New Generic; 2 Clinton Park San Francisco, CA; 1984-07-19; 8.5x17 -- Snakefinger's Vestal Virgins, Frightwig, Polkacide, Bambi; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-11; 8.5x17.
    8. Shiva Dancing [Shiva Dancing [Siva Dancing]]; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-18; 8.5x17.
    9. Convictions, The Stickers, Stingers; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-23; 8.5x17.
    10. PGR, The Brickmen, Tupelo Chain Sex; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-17; 8.5x17.
    11. Plastic Medium, Screen Of Dreams; Upper Grant Club; 1525 Grant Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1983-04-28; 8.5x17.
    12. Ecco Race; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-01; 8.5x17.
    13. Black Athletes, Ku Ku Ku, Glorious Din, Stick Against Stone, Rhythm Pigs, Schrödinger's Cat; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-23; 8.5x17.
    14. American Music Club [AMC], The Naked Into, Ugly Stick; Soma Gallery; 12th St. at Howard San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-01; 8.5x17.
  - Folder 17, 1984- 1986 (Box 3)
    1. Debra Knox Band, The Edge, Lost Souls; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; November 6; 8.5x17.
    2. Rage Of Eden; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-07; 8.5x17.
    3. Rhythm Pigs, Honeymooners; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-05; 8.5x17.
    4. Pop-O-Pies; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-22; 8.5x17.
    5. 7 Dutch Poets, The Witnesses, Housecoat Project, Mess Tent; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-08; 8.5x17.
    6. New Breed; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-08; 8.5x17.
    7. Jungle Dinner, Black Athletes, Three Mouse Guitars; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; July 6; 8.5x17.
    8. Jet Boy, Doll (from L.A.), sea hags; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-13 -- Jet Boy, Sea Hags; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-15; 8.5x17.
    9. Jimmy Baker, Misled, The Witnesses, Steven Moore Project; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-10-03; 8.5x17.
    10. Mrs. Green; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-22; 8.5x17.
    11. Pray For Rain, Impulse F, Boxing Factory (formerly Paris Working); V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-07; 8.5x17.
    12. The Defectors; San Francisco Art Institute; 800 Chestnut St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-14; 8.5x17.
    13. The Defectors; Sound Of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; 8.5x17.
  - Folder 18, 1984- 1986 (Box 3)
    1. The Defectors; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-03-01; 8.5x17.
    2. The Defectors, Annie Arbgast; Reject Club; 1550 California St. San Francisco, CA; October 31; 8.5x17.
    3. The Defectors; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-02-18; 8.5x17.
    4. The Defectors; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-02-20; 8.5x17.
    5. Mr. Lucky; The Next; 201 9th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-22; 8.5x17.
    6. Bliss Colb, Ned Van Alstyne, "Bob" Venezia, Jeff Walker; Studio Eremos; 401 Alabama St. San Francisco, CA; October 31 - November 16; 8.5x17.
    7. Necropolis Of Love, Until December, DJ Greg Silvia; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-18; 8.5x17.
    8. The Angel of Thorns; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-10-04; 8.5x17.
  - Folder 1, 1983- 1986 (Box 4)
    1. Voices; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-01-26; 9x12.
    2. [multi-color image of cowboy on horse with sunset]; 9x12.
    3. The New Ice Age; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-27; 5x16.5.
    4. Bird Killers, Sea Hags; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-06 -- Bird Killers, Sea Hags, Angst; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-29; 11x13.
    5. Faye Spain; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-12 -- Barking Spiders; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-15; 11x17.
    6. The Mysteries; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-21; 11x17.
    7. Sea Hags, Altar De Fey; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-02 -- M-1 Alternative, Dean Street; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA;1986-01-05; 11x17.
    8. The Whitefronts, DJ David Bassin; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-15; 11x17.
    9. Legal Reins; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-21; 11x17.
    10. Monkey Rhythm, Orange Curtain; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-06 -- Voluntary Living; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-08; 11x17.
    11. The Morlocks; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-13 -- Barking Spiders; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-15; 11x17.
    12. Nimbus, House Of Wheels, Wages Of Sin, Half Church; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-22; 11x17.
    13. Zula Pool; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-01; 11x17.
    14. Big City, Mojo Nixon, Shy Hands; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-16; 11x17.
    15. Big City, Zulu Spear, DJ Jonathan E.; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-31; 11x17.
    16. Big Race, Screen Of Dreams; The Stud; 1535 Folsom St. San Francisco, CA; 1983-04-03; 11x17.
    17. [many]; Roxie Theatre; 3117 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11; 11x17.
    18. Big City, The Looters; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-25; 11x17.
    19. Pig Latin, Spot 1019, 3 Mouse Guitars, The Leopard Set, Ju Ju Box, Danny Williams (Comedian); The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-21; 11x17.
    20. Linda Tillery And Her Band, Grupo Matica; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-21.
  - Folder 2, 1983- 1986 (Box 4)
    1. Frank Garvey; Modern Times Bookstore; 968 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-01-04; 11x17.
    2. Blue Planet; Lumiere Theatre; 1572 California St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-10; 11x17.
    3. Theosomorphia. Symphonie Melancholie Des Vampyres, Bleeding Catholic Children. Theatre Des Vampyres; San Francisco Art Institute Lecture Hall; 800 Chestnut St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-05; 11x17.
    4. A Team, Beast, If Then Why; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1983-05-21; 11x17.
    5. The Looters, Unruly World, Tricobra; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-05; 11x17.
    6. Samba Party! Come Dance to The Hot Rhythms Of Samba, Played By A Batucada Percussion Group And Special Guest Performers; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-16; 11x17.
    7. Black Athletes, Voices; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-15; 11x17.
    8. Black Athletes; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-18; 11x17.
    9. Black Athletes, Teknofear; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-31; 11x17.
    10. Dance At Wolfgang's. A Month Of Dancing, Videos & Fun! Upstairs At Wolfgang's, Downstairs At Noma; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986; 11x17.
    11. Screen Of Dreams, Big Race; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; May 21; 11x17.
    12. Ku Ku Ku, Tripod Jimmie, Pig Latin; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-01; 11x17.
    13. Les Nickelettes. Oh Goddess!; The Lab; 1805 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985; 11x17.
    14. Lethal Gospel, Yo, Sea Hags; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-17; 11x17.
    15. The Invertebrates; On Broadway [Ozone On Broadway]; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-10-03; 11x17.
    16. The Invertebrates, Arms of Venus, The Job; Club Foot; 2520 3rd St. San Francisco, CA; September 21; 11x17.
    17. The New Ice Age, See Page II; Chi Chi Club; 440 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-14; 11x17.
    18. Sin; Sound Of Music; 162 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-30 -- Sin; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-01; 11x17.
    19. Peace Or Perish Multi-Media Rock Marathon. Benefit For Peace Or Perish - A Crisis Anthology. 50 Rock Bands; Art Exhibit; 59 Performing Poets; Personal Appearance By Miriam Patchen; film; Video Screenings; Light Show; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1983-12; 11x17.
    20. Flagship I-Beam 1. The Ultimate In Dance, Live Shows, And San Francisco's Finest Video And Only Laser Spectacular; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 11x17.
    21. Bathhouse Benediction, Dream Man; Theatre Rhinoceros; 2926 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10; 11x17.
  - Folder 3, 1983- 1986 (Box 3)
    1. Winston Tong; Club Nine [Artmotel Number Nine]; 399 9th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-15; 11x17.
    2. [many]; Foot Work Studio; Club Nine; The Lab; San Francisco, CA; March 18-April 18; 11x17.
    3. Poison Gas Research, Black Swans; Martin/Weber Gallery; 220 8th St. San Francisco, CA; September 21; 11x17.
    4. Frightwig, The Afflicted, Psychic Orphans, Celebrity Skin, Baby Jesus And The Housecoat Contingents, Buck Naked And The Barebottom Boys; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-18; 11x17.
    5. Gone World; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-05; 11x17.
    6. Norman Salant, Ben Bossi, Terra Incognita; Hotel Utah; 584 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-05; 11x17.
    7. Mary Virginia Marsh, Teresa Marie Schmittroth, Tina Marie Romanak, Theresa Marie Wagner; 1640 7th St. Gallery; 1640 7th St. Oakland, CA; April 25-May 23, 1986; 11x17.
    8. Rafael Montes; San Francisco, CA; 11x17.
    9. Flat Lands; Artists' Television Access (ATA); 220 8th St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-15; 5.5x17.
    10. Blue Ruin, Farmers; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; October 21; 11x17.
    11. Terra Incognita, The Invertebrates, Pamela Z; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-22; 11x17.
    12. Green On Red, Flying Color, The Ophelias, The McGuires; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1983-04-08; 11x17.
    13. Sparks; Kabuki Nightclub; 1881 Post St. San Francisco, CA; 1983-04-08 -- Depeche Mode; Kabuki Nightclub; 1881 Post St. San Francisco, CA; 1983-03-29 -- Thompson Twins; Kabuki Nightclub; 1881 Post St. San Francisco, CA; 1983-03-30 -- Ultravox; Kabuki Nightclub; 1881 Post St. San Francisco, CA; 1983-04-07; 11x17.
    14. Faith No More, Glorious Din, Electric Piece, 23 Screams; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-20; 11x17.
    15. Mink DeVille, Preston Smith And The Crocodiles; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; April 7-8; 11x17.
    16. Chuck Berry, Mitch Woods & His Rocket 88s; The Keystone; 2119 University Ave. Berkeley, CA; 1984-02-02 -- Chuck Berry; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1984-02-04; 11x17.
    17. Glorious Din, Cabaret Voltaire Video, Survival Research Laboratory Video; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-04-18; 11x17.
    18. The English Beat, The Blasters, DJ Howie Klein; San Francisco Civic Center; 99 Grove St. San Francisco, CA; 1982-12-11; 11x17.
    19. Flying Color, Camper Van Beethoven, The Cat Heads, Fields Laughing; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-15; 11x17.
    20. The Grateful Dead; San Francisco Civic Center; 99 Grove St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12; 11x17.
  - Folder 4, 1984- 1986 (Box 4)
    1. Rock My Religion; Martin/Weber Gallery; 220 8th St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-09-28; 11x17.
    2. The Cure; Henry J. Kaiser Convention Center; 10 10th St. Oakland, CA; 1985-10-09 -- The Cure; San Jose Civic Auditorium; 135 W. San Carlos St. San Jose, CA; 1985-10-06; 11x17.
    3. R.E.M., Renegades, If Then Why; Old Waldorf; 444 Battery St. San Francisco, CA; 1983-06-14; 11x17.
    4. Simple Minds; Kabuki Nightclub; 1881 Post St. San Francisco, CA; 1983-04-12; 11x17.
    5. U.K. Subs; P.A. [Keystone Palo Alto?]; Palo Alto?, CA; 1985-05-06 [?] -- U.K. Subs; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-05-07; 11x17.
    6. Toy Dolls, Frightwig, Jet Boy; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-19; 11x17.
    7. Red Lorry Yellow Lorry, Tripod Jimmie; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; April 28; 11x17.
    8. Faith No More, Glorious Din, Morally Bankrupt, Infant Bonds Of Joy, Thought Factory; Golden Gate Park, Marx Meadow; San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-01; 11x17.
    9. Thrill Of The Pull; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-09; 11x17.
    10. Wages Of Sin; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-17; 11x17.
    11. The Naked Into; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-03; 11x17.
    12. The Naked Into; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-25; 11x17.
    13. Thrill Of The Pull; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-28; 11x17.
    14. Thrill Of The Pull; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11; 11x17.
    15. Bam Bam; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-04; 11x17.
    16. Voluntary Living; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12 -- Mrs. Green; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-05; 11x17.
    17. Until December, Sea Hags; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; October 31; 11x17.
    18. Zula Pool; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-11; 11x17.
    19. Monkey Rhythm, DJ David Bassin; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-01; 11x17.
    20. Necropolis Of Love, DJ David Bassin; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-24; 11x17.
    21. Terminal Man, Small Cognito; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-28; 11x17.
  - Folder 5, 1985- 1986 (Box 4)
    1. My Sin, DJ David Bassin; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-08; 11x17.
    2. Yo; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-16; 11x17.
    3. Love Club; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-02; 11x17.
    4. The Monikers, Barking Spiders; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-23; 11x17.
    5. Mrs. Green; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-18; 11x17.
    6. Blue Movie, Terra Incognita; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-20; 11x17.
    7. The Class; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-05-12; 11x17.
    8. The Morlocks; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-03; 11x17.
    9. Shy Hands; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-22; 11x17.
    10. Saqqara Dogs; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-10; 11x17.
    11. Chris Isaak Silvertone, Iguana Twist; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12 -- The Monikers; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12; 11x17.
    12. Chris Isaak Silvertone; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12; 11x17.
    13. The Defectors; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11-29; 11x17.
    14. The Morlocks, The Miracle Workers, Sea Hags, Brotherhood Of Light, DJ Barry St. Vitus (KALX); Swedish American Hall; 2174 Market St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-09-08; 11x17.
    15. Monkey Rhythm, Lords Of The New Church, Crawl Away Machine; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-04-27; 11x17.
    16. Flying Color; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-06; 8.5x5.5.
    17. Maxine Howard; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-31; 11x17.
    18. Meditations (Reggae Band), Rhythm-O-Matics (World Beat), Intergalactic Funkateers (Hip Hop); Russian Hall; 2460 Sutter St. San Francisco, CA; 11x17.
    19. Freddie McGregor, John Holt, Sister Carol, Ini Kamoze, Studio One Band, Raskiddus Roots Connection; Booker T. Washington Community Center; 800 Presidio Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-01-04; 11x17.
    20. The Mud Dogs; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-11; 11x17.
  - Folder 6, 1984- 1986 (Box 4)
    1. Missing Persons, The Tubes, Eddie And The Tide; Stanford University, Frost Amphitheater; Palo Alto, CA; 1984-10-06; 11x17.
    2. The Looters, Zulu Spear; Great American Music Hall; 859 O'Farrell St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-04-26; 11x17.
    3. Jean Cocteau Festival; Roxie Theatre; 3117 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-08; 11x17.
    4. The Rhythm-O-Matics; Escovedo's; 3285 Lakeshore Ave. Oakland, CA; 1985-12-26; 11x17.
    5. Gallery-Dance Club-Bar; The Basement; 600 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-05-04; 11x17.
    6. Boomba, A Noi-z Groove; The Basement; 600 Turk St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-05-04; 11x17.
    7. [line drawing of tangled mechanical figures, with note from Scott to Todd on back about postcard artwork]; 11x11.
    8. Oasis III. The Third Year Is Coming [etc.] In Celebration Of Our Second Yerar Anniversary; The Oasis; 298 11th St. San Francisco, CA; 11x17.
    9. Patsy Cline & The Memphis G Spots, Nonfiction; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-03 -- Scraping Foetus Off The Wheel, Negativeland; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-10 -- Robyn Hitchcock; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-17; 11x17.
    10. When The Wind Blows; Buriel Clay Memorial Theatre at the Western Addition Cultural Center; 762 Fulton St. San Francisco, CA; 1986; 11x17.
    11. The Rhythm-O-Matics; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-14; 11x17.
    12. Red Rockers; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1983-07-04; 11x17.
    13. Mrs. Green; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; January 9; 11x17.
    14. The Replacements, Flying Color, The Cat Heads; The Filmore; 1805 Geary Blvd. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-03; 11x17.
    15. Beyonda Dagger; Baybrick Inn; 1190 Folsom St. San Francisco, CA; March 10 & 24; 11x17.
    16. Sea Hags, The Morlocks; Swedish American Hall; 2174 Market St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-31; 11x14.
    17. The Corner of the Eye; Theatre Rhinoceros; 2926 16th St. San Francisco, CA; Wed.-Sun. April 26-June 1 [?]; 11x17.
    18. Caribbean Allstars, Vision; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-07-07; 11x17.
    19. Alma Tropical, Mariachi Los Gavilanes con Luisa Fernandez, Los Lupenos, Xipetotec, Luis Julia Con Rafael Manriquez, Jose Luis Orozco, Matica; Mission High School Auditorium; 3750 18th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-20; 11x15.5.
    20. El Grupo Sexo, Fishbone; Spatz; 16903 Algonquin St. Huntington Beach, CA; 1984-10-12 -- El Grupo Sexo, Red Hot Chili Peppers; Spatz; 16903 Algonquin St. Huntington Beach, CA; 1985-09-06 -- El Grupo Sexo, The Offenders; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-08 -- El Grupo Sexo; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-07; 11x17.
  - Folder 7, 1984- 1986 (Box 4)
    1. Ritual Band, The [16 people listed, including John Gruntfest]; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-09-24; 11x17 -- Party Of Five; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-04; 11x17.
    2. New Breed, The Razers; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-08; 11x17.
    3. Translator, The Girl Can't Help It, Night Owls; [Soma Gallery?]; 12th St. at Howard San Francisco, CA; 1984-10-06; 11x17.
    4. Parri Troy; Club Nine; 399 9th St. San Francisco, CA; 11x17.
    5. Too Much Fun; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-06; 11x17.
    6. KBC. Kantner Balin Casady Band, Stick Against Stone; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-16; 11x17.
    7. Mrs. Green; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; June 29; 11x17.
    8. Trial, Glorious Din; International Building; 50 Oak St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-03-14; 11x17.
    9. Shy Hands, Nu Shooz; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-05-08; 11x17.
    10. Shy Hands; Nightbreak; 1821 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-17; 11x17.
    11. Shy Hands, Big City; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-17; 11x17.
    12. Typhoon, Psychic Orphans; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-24; 11x17.
    13. The Snapp; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-20; 11x17.
    14. Specimen, Xtasy Party, The Bastards Sons of God; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 11x17.
    15. Swelele and Out-A-Grass Posse, Ridim Section, Flaming Limbo, Strictly Roots, Caribbean Allstars, Frontline Rockers, Nite Owl Disco, Julian Harker; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-20; 11x17.
    16. New Breed, Noonday Underground, Soul Kitchen w/ DJ Liz Pepin; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-04-04; 11x17.
    17. Ten Tall Men, Sound Policy; Berkeley Square; 1333 University Ave. Berkeley, CA; 1985-08-27; 11x17.
    18. Terry Riley, Krishna Bhatt; St. John's Presbyterian Church; 2727 College Ave. Berkeley, CA; April 13; 11x17.
    19. Girls - Boys - New Wave - Rock - Punk - Reggae - Ska[etc.]; Wolfgang's; 901 Columbus Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1984-02; 11x17.
    20. A Modern Tradition. Celebrate Gay Pride Week; Trocadero Transfer; 520 4th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-06-30; 11x17.
  - Folder 8, 1984- 1986 (Box 4)
    1. Fish Music; When You Discover Fish Music You Discover A New Clear World. Look for "Fear Of Accidents" and "It's A New Clear World" In The New Future; 11x17.
    2. Palmetto State; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-25 -- Palmetto State; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-22; 11x17.
    3. Prince Joni And The Beat Featuring Joni Haastrup, Anne Earthling & The Planets; Full Moon Saloon; 1725 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-01-10; 11x17.
    4. Prince Joni And The World Beat Jam Featuring Joni Haastrup, Mapenzi; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-12-01; 11x17.
    5. Terra Incognita, Tribal Warning Theater; Gumption Theater; 1563 Page St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-14 -- Terra Incognita; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-06 -- Terra Incognita; Mabuhay Gardens; 443 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-19 -- Terra Incognita; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-02-21; 11x17.
    6. Slantstep; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 11x17.
    7. On Location 1984. Four Temporary Art Installations in Downtown Oakland's Victorian Row; Oakland, CA; 1984-09; 11x17.
    8. Hanging Party, Code Of The West, Boss Hoss, G.T. Jesus; [Capp Street Center]; 362 Capp St. San Francisco, CA; 1986-04-19; 11x17.
    9. Glorious Din, Morally Bankrupt, 23 Screams, Mechanical Bride; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-05-21; 11x17.
    10. Jet Boy; On Broadway; 435 Broadway San Francisco, CA; October 31; 11x17.
    11. Crawl Away Machine, Primus; Graffiti; 853 Valencia St. San Francisco, CA; 1985-01-26; 11x17.
    12. The Crunch; The Stone; 412 Broadway San Francisco, CA; 1985-08-21; 11x17.
    13. The Brickmen; 16th Note; 3160 16th St. San Francisco, CA; 1984-12-30; 11x17.
    14. The Contractions, Mr. Clean; I-Beam; 1748 Haight St. San Francisco, CA; 1982-10-18; 11x17.
    15. Ku Ku Ku, Black Athletes; V.I.S. Club; 628 Divisadero St. San Francisco, CA; January 31; 11x17.
    16. Social Unrest, Screamin' Sirens, Poison 13, Sea Hags, The Weasels; The Farm; 1499 Potrero Ave. San Francisco, CA; 1985-10-12; 11x14.5.